smackdownvsraw.com 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ONEsite.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User").

**Privacy**

Users' privacy is very important to ONEsite.com. ONEsite.com is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to ONEsite.com. This Web site is not directed at children under 13 years of age.

**The Information We Collect**

ONEsite.com may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering productsand services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. ONEsite.com may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users' PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

**How We Use Information**

ONEsite.com may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by ONEsite.com and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with ONEsite.com and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. Domain Registration details as required by the Registry Operator will be shared with the Registry and the Registry may in turn share said information per its policies or allow public access to information such as whois type domain information. ONEsite.com may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of ONEsite.com, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.

**Disclosure of Information**

ONEsite.com may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of ONEsite.com business.

**Maintenance of Information**

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

**European Union, Safe Harbor Compliance**

ONEsite is Safe Harbor compliant, for our Safe Harbor policy, click here.

**Questions**

Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to [support@onesite.com](mailto:support@onesite.com).
